export const data = [
    {
        question: "What does Ikhfah mean?",
        option1: "To Make Clear",
        option2: "To Bounce",
        option3: "To Stretch",
        option4: "To Hide",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ikhfah applied to?",
        option1: "Throat Letters",
        option2: "Noon Saakinah and Tanween",
        option3: "Ikhfah",
        option4: "Qalqalah",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How many letters of Ikhfah are there? ",
        option1: "5",
        option2: "15",
        option3: "2",
        option4: "7",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What are the two ways of making Ikhfah?",
        option1: "Tafkheem and Tarqeeq",
        option2: "Qalqalah Letters",
        option3: "Any of the Throat Letters",
        option4: "غ",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the correct example for Ikhfah with a Noon Saakin",
        option1: "من يعمل",
        option2: "من بعد",
        option3: "عليم حكيم",
        option4: "أنْزل",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "Choose the example for Ikhfah with a Tanween",
        option1: "من يعمل",
        option2: "رَسُولا شهيدا",
        option3: "عليم حكيم",
        option4: "من شرّ",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What does Tafkheem mean?",
        option1: "Heavy Letters",
        option2: "Qalqalah Letters",
        option3: "Any of the Throat Letters",
        option4: "غ",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What does Tarqeeq mean?",
        option1: "Tafkheem and Tarqeeq",
        option2: "Qalqalah Letters",
        option3: "Light Letters",
        option4: "غ",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What do we do before saying the Ikhfah letter?",
        option1: "Merge The Letters",
        option2: "Qalqalah Letters",
        option3: "Bounce The Letter",
        option4: "Make Ghunnah",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What does Ghunnah mean?",
        option1: "Nasalisation",
        option2: "To Make Clear",
        option3: "Light Letters",
        option4: "Make Ghunnah",
        ans: 1,
    },

]